作词 : aimerrhythm
作曲 : Rui Momota
编曲 : 玉井健二/百田留衣
Ye Ye
It's always in my heart
你一直都在我心里
寝過ごしたまま 日曜の朝
睡过头的周日 赖在床上
なんて素敵な日差しに
阳光是那么的美好
今が永遠なんて おおげさ いつもそう
说什么此刻就是永恒 你总是这么夸张
ふいに出た声に照れくさそうに そっと君は笑う
然后悄悄地 腼腆的笑着
Oh, Daisy you, you could make me feel
Daisy 你让我感觉到
How beautiful
一切都那么的美好
Sometimes make me fool
有时也让我变得有点儿迟钝
Ah babe girl, in our comfy room
亲爱的女孩儿 窝在我们舒适的房间里
I' m in the mood for kissing more
迫不及待想要亲吻
All I need is falling for you now
此刻只想为你沉沦
Oh,Daisy, it's true
Oh Daisy 都是真的
It's always in my heart
你一直都在我心里
ありふれた部屋  一輪の花
你是这平庸房间里的一朵花
カ一テン揺れてる 窓辺に
摆放在窗帘随风飘动的窗边
君の手に触れたく て おどけて  いつもそう
想要牵着你的手 像往常一样逗你开心
二人きり部屋で 午後の予定も  ずっとまとまらない
在只有两人的房间里 虽然午后的计划一直没达成一致
Oh，Daisy you, you could make me feel
Oh Daisy 你让我感觉到
How beautiful
一切都那么的美好
Sometimes make me fool
有时也让我变得有点儿迟钝
Ah babe girl, in our comfy room
亲爱的女孩儿 窝在我们舒适的房间里
I' m in the mood for kissing more
迫不及待想要亲吻
All I need is falling for you now
此刻只想为你沉沦
Oh,Daisy, it's true
Oh Daisy 都是真的
repeat
君を乗せ 自転車は進む
骑着自行车载着你前进
何もない午後と 南風が誘う空へ
在平静的午后 南风应约而来向着天空
Oh,Daisy you, you could make me feel
Oh Daisy 你让我感觉到
How beautiful
I don't know what to say
我不知道该说什么
Oh Baby girl, you are my comfy room
亲爱的女孩儿 你就是我最温馨的小窝
I'll be the one to tell that truth
我将成为向你倾诉真相的那个人
All I need is falling for you now
此刻只想为你沉沦
Daisy, you
Daisy 你...
I tell that truth
我说的都是真心话
AII I need is falling for you now
此刻只想为你沉沦
Oh，Daisy. you
Oh Daisy 你...
Ye Ye